{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263137142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263137142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263142411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263142411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263146892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263146892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263152572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263152572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263157319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263157319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263162889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263162889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263168554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263168554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263173859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263173859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263178075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263178075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263183130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263183130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263188085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263188085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263194618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263194617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 9776904e-b631-4d5d-8c52-d203a2db6cd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263206379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263206378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263210119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263210119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263211686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263211686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263215970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263215970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263217577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263217577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263221266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263221266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263222874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263222873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263227128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263227128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263229149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263229149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263229301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263229300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 46d785bf-50a1-4bd3-b2df-0834698b592e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263240774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263240774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263244147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263244147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263245711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263245710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263249451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263249451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263251014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263251014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263254335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263254335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263255906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263255905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263259493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263259492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263261500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263261499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263261664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263261664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263268175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263268175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7aa6e42d-0e62-43ac-9171-2b741ee6a53d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263278459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263278459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263278882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263278881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263279122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263279122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263279444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263279443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263279684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263279683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263283166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263283166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263283465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263283465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263284369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263284369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263284792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263284792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263287708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263287708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263288001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263288000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263288858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263288858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263289533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263289533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263290280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263290280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263290611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263290610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263290893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263290892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263291213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263291213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263291481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263291481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263295256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263295255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263295651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263295650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263295890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263295890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263296211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263296211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263296453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263296453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263299948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263299948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263300251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263300251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263301171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263301170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263301601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263301601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263304541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263304541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263304832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263304831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263305685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263305685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263306363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263306363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263307106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263307106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263307447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263307447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263307728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263307728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263308062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263308062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263308342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263308342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263311788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263311787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263311886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263311886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 83eb2c80-fd6c-4453-b66e-a7cafaecb490"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263325733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263325733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263330094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263330094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263335004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263335004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263340343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263340343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263345802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263345802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263351055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263351055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263356409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263356409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263362169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263362169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263368758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263368758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263374199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263374199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263379101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263379101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263384355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263384354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263391063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263391061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 5dafb061-fdf3-40e3-8f77-c02327facd3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263413404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263413403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_e_i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263420048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263420048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_o_i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263426666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263426666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_u_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263433292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263433291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_o_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263439932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263439931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263446565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263446565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_u_a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263453219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263453219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_e_i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263459831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263459831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_i_a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263466462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263466462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_i_o"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263473085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263473084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_i_a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263486224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263486224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0d843aa5-fbb4-4f85-b0f8-082676eac026"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_I..I.vow.10.rand.say.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_e_i_a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263569674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263569673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_panda-iwapo-chungwa-panda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263590810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263590810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_dhaifu-chungwa-subira-fahari"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263625379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263625379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_damu-hizi-acha-manjano"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263644079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263644079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_twende-a-manjano-kali"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263661763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263661763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_kijani-uko-taratibu-gani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263678737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263678737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_kile-kijani-macho-taratibu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263697216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263697215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_manjano-tazama-maridadi-samawati"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263700944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263700944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_manjano-tazama-maridadi-samawati"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" samawati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263717593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263717593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_maridadi-samawati-manjano-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263720825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263720825"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_maridadi-samawati-manjano-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" samawati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263741366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263741366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_kaka-tazama-nili-yu"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" kaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263745546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263745546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_kaka-tazama-nili-yu"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" tazama"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263748804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263748804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_kaka-tazama-nili-yu"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" nili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263766044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263766044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_umbo-nili-pumua-dhaifu"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" pumua"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263773021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263773021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_umbo-nili-pumua-dhaifu"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" umbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263775990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263775989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_umbo-nili-pumua-dhaifu"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" dhaifu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263779170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263779170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_umbo-nili-pumua-dhaifu"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" dhaifu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263782376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263782376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_umbo-nili-pumua-dhaifu"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" dhaifu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263785060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263785060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_umbo-nili-pumua-dhaifu"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" pumua"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263787744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263787743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_umbo-nili-pumua-dhaifu"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" nili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263804269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263804269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zambarau_taja-cheza-ata-zambarau"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zambarau"," userResponse":" zambarau"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263825065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263825063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zambarau_taja-cheza-ata-zambarau"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263825261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263825261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 28946d35-fbd5-4303-a6cc-59992382237a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za ____________?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263836187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263836186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263838855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263838855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263840407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263840407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263843378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263843378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263844926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263844926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263848230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263848230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263849784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263849784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263852908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263852908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263854456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263854456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263857223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263857223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263859236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263859235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263859400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263859400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ccc0e3b7-40b0-4113-b6f2-575a272ef3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263871736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263871736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263876811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263876811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263885032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263885032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-7-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263891087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263891087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263895800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263895800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263902153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263902152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263908542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263908541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263913538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263913538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263920706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263920706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-9-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263926442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263926441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263933086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263933085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fef54b8f-532e-4b4c-a1f2-dc157f0bf093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263943172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263943172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8a81707e-ed06-4bf5-907b-82e7cbe0bb26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-a-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263947748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263947748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8a81707e-ed06-4bf5-907b-82e7cbe0bb26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263951324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263951324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8a81707e-ed06-4bf5-907b-82e7cbe0bb26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-u-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263954298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263954297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8a81707e-ed06-4bf5-907b-82e7cbe0bb26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263957522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263957521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8a81707e-ed06-4bf5-907b-82e7cbe0bb26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263963261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263963259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8a81707e-ed06-4bf5-907b-82e7cbe0bb26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263993246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263993246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7c7724fa-0cda-4d8c-b311-ab0db26c0254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakati_wakati-baada-kwenda-katika"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wakati"," userResponse":" wakati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264016981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264016981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7c7724fa-0cda-4d8c-b311-ab0db26c0254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakati_wakati-mimi-katika-karibu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wakati"," userResponse":" wakati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264067545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264067540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7c7724fa-0cda-4d8c-b311-ab0db26c0254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakati_wakati-mimi-katika-karibu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264067636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264067636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7c7724fa-0cda-4d8c-b311-ab0db26c0254"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264079366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264079365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" omba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264084280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264084279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" omba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264085873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264085873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264091524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264091523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264093145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264093145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264097087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264097087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264098681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264098681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" oa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264102403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264102402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" oa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264103965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264103965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" osha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264107723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264107722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" osha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264109367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264109367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264113901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264113901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264115485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264115484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264118394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264118394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264120402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264120402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264120485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264120485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a4c6b74-9abc-4779-9a3c-e1fb65db9c4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264140964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264140964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264141958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264141957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264142283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264142282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264142437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264142437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264145960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264145960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264146474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264146473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264150011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264150011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264150913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264150913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264155430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264155430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264160946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264160946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264169585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264169585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264177993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264177993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264183938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264183938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264192217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264192217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264198761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264198761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264200759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264200758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 7469b238-299f-43d8-ab1b-feb86b646a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264210904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264210904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264214438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264214438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-e-u"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264217385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264217385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-a"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264220713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264220712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-o-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264223868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264223868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264227357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264227357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-e-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264232099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264232099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-o-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264235390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264235390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_a-o-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264240604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264240604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-a-o"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264243818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264243818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264249569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264249568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 4342e530-728d-42e4-834f-70e93051e7a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264270357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264270357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-e-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264273299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264273299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-e-u"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264277138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264277138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-o-a"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264280994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264280994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264285255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264285255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-a-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264289892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264289892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264294787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264294787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264297984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264297984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-o-e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264301782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264301782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_a-o-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264304912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264304911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264310642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264310641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6afa3e21-6e7c-4b5c-a636-7a3233808798"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264322549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264322548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-e-u"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264326302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264326301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-o-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264331042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264331041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_a-o-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264336614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264336614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264339847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264339847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-o-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264344484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264344484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264350194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264350194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264355826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264355826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264359810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264359810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-e-o"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264364398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264364398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-a-o"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264367607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264367607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264373353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264373352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e081e4a7-a4c2-4fa9-8bbd-e6578e7971c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264406106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264406105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" f62fe851-d432-42b6-8eae-f36b665b78a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtini_vyangu-aina-mlima-mtini"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mtini"," userResponse":" mtini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264433610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264433610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" f62fe851-d432-42b6-8eae-f36b665b78a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njia_mbali-mbaya-bado-njia"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" njia"," userResponse":" njia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264454333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264454333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" f62fe851-d432-42b6-8eae-f36b665b78a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku_kuwa-nyumbani-siku-kutoka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" siku"," userResponse":" siku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264474873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264474873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" f62fe851-d432-42b6-8eae-f36b665b78a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njia_hapa-njia-ule-ah"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" njia"," userResponse":" njia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264498093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264498093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" f62fe851-d432-42b6-8eae-f36b665b78a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka_kabla-nina-Nyoka-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Nyoka"," userResponse":" Nyoka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264518804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264518804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" f62fe851-d432-42b6-8eae-f36b665b78a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa_ziwa-kuu-sura-binadamu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwa"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264532443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264532440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" f62fe851-d432-42b6-8eae-f36b665b78a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ziwa_ziwa-kuu-sura-binadamu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264532567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264532567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" f62fe851-d432-42b6-8eae-f36b665b78a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264543155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264543155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17c6eea5-472a-4658-b5a3-0ebaa7011423"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-a-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264546516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264546516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17c6eea5-472a-4658-b5a3-0ebaa7011423"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264549903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264549903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17c6eea5-472a-4658-b5a3-0ebaa7011423"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-u-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264552765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264552765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17c6eea5-472a-4658-b5a3-0ebaa7011423"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264556132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264556132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17c6eea5-472a-4658-b5a3-0ebaa7011423"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264561920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264561919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17c6eea5-472a-4658-b5a3-0ebaa7011423"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264571561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264571561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-4-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264575969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264575968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-8-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264581697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264581697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264586142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264586142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264590695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264590694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-4-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264594951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264594950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-0-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264599607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264599607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264603954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264603953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_5-8-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264609152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264609152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264613642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264613641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-9-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264619752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264619752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-9-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264626380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264626379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 6454b9f1-7541-4bd0-8fbe-0a61e92c2ebb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-9-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264636999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264636999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264638025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264638025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264640687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264640687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264642480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264642480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264645200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264645200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264646236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264646236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264649392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264649392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264650428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264650428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264653256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264653256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264654293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264654293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264657502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264657502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264657663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264657663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2a7e6e66-3ca6-4cb6-b3d2-67769af92b69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264668616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264668616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264669482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264669482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264670508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264670508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264670755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264670754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264671330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264671329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264671924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264671924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264672473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264672472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264676320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264676320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264677069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264677068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264677472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264677472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264678290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264678290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264679364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264679364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264680158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264680158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264683424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264683424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264684968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264684968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264687992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264687992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264688266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264688266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264688990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264688990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264689795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264689795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264690249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264690249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264690943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264690943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264691667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264691667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264692863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264692863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264696510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264696510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264697573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264697573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" ANAPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264698106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264698106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264698708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264698708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264701495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264701495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264701608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264701608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 8fe434af-da22-4337-b1bf-ede19c2dea60"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264710642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264710641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ca14c25e-415e-4ea0-b143-184a3d202b0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-d-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264716617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264716617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ca14c25e-415e-4ea0-b143-184a3d202b0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-d-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264720491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264720491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ca14c25e-415e-4ea0-b143-184a3d202b0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-p-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264723948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264723948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ca14c25e-415e-4ea0-b143-184a3d202b0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-w-r"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264727352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264727352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ca14c25e-415e-4ea0-b143-184a3d202b0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264731434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264731434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ca14c25e-415e-4ea0-b143-184a3d202b0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264737188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264737187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ca14c25e-415e-4ea0-b143-184a3d202b0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264743438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264743438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" b61203c4-45c5-4640-856b-f5ff675eeaba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264755311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264755311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" b61203c4-45c5-4640-856b-f5ff675eeaba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264757784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264757783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" b61203c4-45c5-4640-856b-f5ff675eeaba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264757923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264757923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" b61203c4-45c5-4640-856b-f5ff675eeaba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264769094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264769094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264772339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264772338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264773917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264773917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ubao"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264777170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264777170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ubao"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264778726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264778726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264781701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264781701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264783260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264783260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uyoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264786945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264786945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uyoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264788497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264788497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264790229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264790229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264791779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264791779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264795234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264795234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264796811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264796811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" udongo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264801032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264801032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" udongo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264802603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264802603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264806233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264806232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264808251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264808250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264808413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264808413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0c81c916-5f0e-4f9c-a352-0963e63b321d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264818187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264818187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264818952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264818952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264819393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264819393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264822286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264822286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264822497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264822497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264823494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264823494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264823823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264823823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264826931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264826930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264827155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264827155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264827859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264827859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264828772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264828771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264830928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264830928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264831424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264831423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264832160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264832160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMA"," userResponse":" MWEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264832783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264832783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264833295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264833294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264834266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264834265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRA"," userResponse":" SUBIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264837929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264837929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOSUKA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOSUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264838401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264838399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264839155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264839153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264840729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264840729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ZINAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264841271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264841271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264845226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264845226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" AMEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264845530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264845530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264846254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264846253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264846537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264846537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264847610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264847610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGIRANGI"," userResponse":" RANGIRANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264850586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264850586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264851365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264851364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264851666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264851665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264851875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264851875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264852487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264852487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264852737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264852736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264853684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264853684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264855132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264855132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264856489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264856489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264857155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264857154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264858035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264858034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264860970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264860970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264862430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264862429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264863367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264863367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISUKIE"," userResponse":" NISUKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264863757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264863757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264864410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264864410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264864920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264864919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264865455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264865454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264865673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264865672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264866442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264866442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264866889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264866887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264870469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264870469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEKUWA"," userResponse":" NINGEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264870781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264870781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264871424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264871424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264872369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264872369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264874122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264874122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" NINGEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264874685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264874685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264875342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264875342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264875565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264875565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264876215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264876213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264879870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264879869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUA"," userResponse":" NITAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264880449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264880449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264881570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264881570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264882161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264882161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264882909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264882909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264883349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264883349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264886122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264886120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264886207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264886207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e2a41c43-3bbf-41a3-921a-977a483b515b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264896489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264896489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264897251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264897251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264898077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264898077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264898977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264898977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264899580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264899579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264900328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264900327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264902839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264902839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264903369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264903369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264904217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264904217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264905182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264905181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264905736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264905736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264906464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264906464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264909418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264909417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264910160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264910160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264910279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264910279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264911714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264911713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264912106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264912106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264912142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264912142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264915858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264915858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264916547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264916547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264917476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264917476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264918349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264918349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264918570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264918570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264918615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264918614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264922836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264922836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264923467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264923467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264923553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264923552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264924328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264924328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264925262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264925262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264926489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264926489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264928782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264928782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264929483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264929483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264929756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264929755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264930830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264930830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264931381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264931381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264931429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264931429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264935834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264935834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264936462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264936462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264937287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264937287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264937422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264937422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264938177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264938177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264939544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264939526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264941982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264941981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264942479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264942479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264943483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264943483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264944352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264944352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264944966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264944966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264945768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264945768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264948927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264948926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264950905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264950903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264951156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264951156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264951549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264951549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264951759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264951758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264952663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264952663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264955502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264955500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264955979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264955978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264956972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264956972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264957167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264957167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264958431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264958431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264959235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264959235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264961827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264961826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264961982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264961982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548264999639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548264999638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 811ffc5f-004c-4a34-a6fc-f7f60a6c680d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265019724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265019723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265026392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265026391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_u_a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265033051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265033051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_i_u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265039706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265039706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_e_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265046368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265046368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265053019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265053019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_u_e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265059677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265059677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_u"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265066289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265066288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265072956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265072956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_u_a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265079633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265079633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_u_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265092750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265092749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 754c10e7-90fe-4abb-a2aa-d6adfb01043e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_o_u_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265102724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265102724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265103346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265103345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265104283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265104283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265104427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265104427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265105138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265105138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265105822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265105822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265106542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265106542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265107130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265107130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265107362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265107361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265107853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265107853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265111273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265111273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265111790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265111790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265112393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265112393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265113213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265113213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265114110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265114110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265117153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265117152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265117584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265117583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265117699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265117699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265118143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265118143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265118655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265118655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265119462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265119461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265120125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265120125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265123326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265123326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265124015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265124014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265125146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265125146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" NINUNULIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265125686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265125686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265125878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265125878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265126502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265126502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265127439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265127439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265128229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265128229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265128919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265128918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265131865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265131865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265132961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265132961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" NINANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265133760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265133760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265133933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265133933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265134368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265134368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265135458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265135458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265136670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265136670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265137439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265137438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265140252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265140251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265140613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265140612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265141398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265141398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265141761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265141761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265142414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265142414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265142954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265142954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265143306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265143306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265143810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265143809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265144662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265144662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265145383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265145382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265145898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265145897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265149281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265149280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265150288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265150288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265150522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265150522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265151084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265151083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265152371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265152371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOBAKI"," userResponse":" ZILIZOBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265152820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265152820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265153581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265153581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265154110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265154110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265154268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265154268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265154868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265154868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265155733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265155733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265159122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265159122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265160504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265160504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265161463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265161463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265164342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265164342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265164418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265164418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 15456752-f4fa-4e34-be1b-556df69c21eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265200596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265200596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 1c9022a1-bfad-47f5-b4d8-c227dc9ca289"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265212286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265212286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 1c9022a1-bfad-47f5-b4d8-c227dc9ca289"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265221610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265221610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 1c9022a1-bfad-47f5-b4d8-c227dc9ca289"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265230589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265230589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 1c9022a1-bfad-47f5-b4d8-c227dc9ca289"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265240131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265240131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 1c9022a1-bfad-47f5-b4d8-c227dc9ca289"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265249449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265249449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 1c9022a1-bfad-47f5-b4d8-c227dc9ca289"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265259590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265259589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 1c9022a1-bfad-47f5-b4d8-c227dc9ca289"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265292378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265292378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 1c9022a1-bfad-47f5-b4d8-c227dc9ca289"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265324059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265324058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265337905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265337904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265344918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265344918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265350348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265350348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265356354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265356354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265364439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265364439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265372353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265372353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265384856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265384856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265394813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265394813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265404998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265404997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265516556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265516556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 44c3b252-3d46-4deb-af85-7b7f24fcd4a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265516642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265516642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 0aeb788e-0134-458b-ba34-5b660d6d6b8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265627248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265627248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ad425c97-1433-423a-a85b-e945b0c02927"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265637554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265637554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ad425c97-1433-423a-a85b-e945b0c02927"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265647108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265647108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ad425c97-1433-423a-a85b-e945b0c02927"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265655740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265655740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ad425c97-1433-423a-a85b-e945b0c02927"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265665433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265665433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ad425c97-1433-423a-a85b-e945b0c02927"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:vow.asc.A..Z.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265675577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265675576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" ad425c97-1433-423a-a85b-e945b0c02927"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_vow.asc.A..Z.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265705852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265705852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265714325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265714325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-11"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265720062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265720062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265724501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265724500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265729120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265729120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265733785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265733785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265738267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265738267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_10-11-12"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265746929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265746928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-13-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265761131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265761131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265767939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265767939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265774469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265774468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 2f403019-9f34-410c-82c7-584f1dc3e304"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265787365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265787365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265789359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265789358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265790949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265790948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265792964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265792963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265794570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265794570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265796840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265796840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265798428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265798428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265810278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265810278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265811859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265811859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265814154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265814154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265816199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265816198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265816318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265816318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265905033","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265905033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d3865b98-15f0-4cba-a949-28afa3c439d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265905143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265905143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 76c3d2df-dd20-4436-bb16-d27dae7eb9c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265917816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265917813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265918867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265918867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265921409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265921409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265922450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265922450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265925423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265925423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265926466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265926466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265932025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265932025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265933084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265933084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265944388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265944388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265945442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265945442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265948653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265948653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265948776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265948776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 99c0857a-1aa3-4ca9-9529-6c2984225fd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265991597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265991597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548265997190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548265997190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266016312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266016312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266025858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266025858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266032843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266032842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266041378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266041378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266049164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266049164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266057664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266057664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266064172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266064172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266069310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266069310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266075937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266075936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 566d9ced-b162-44a1-aca2-38c41d2a3551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266270703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266270703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 57183fe7-2924-4690-8644-583d62e2fce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266305693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266305693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 57183fe7-2924-4690-8644-583d62e2fce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266313602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266313601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 57183fe7-2924-4690-8644-583d62e2fce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.5.asc.say.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266321287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266321285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 57183fe7-2924-4690-8644-583d62e2fce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_vow.asc.A..Z.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266333293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266333293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266338784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266338784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266343840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266343840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_9-10-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266548648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266548648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-11"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266568312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266568312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-12"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266574424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266574424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266582498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266582498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266587018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266587018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_13-4-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266605615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266605615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266611078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266611077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266617815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266617814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 3b123f54-bf99-480e-a1a8-d518a6196ba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266629114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266629114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266642577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266642577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266650491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266650491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266670097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266670097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266683852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266683851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266691576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266691576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266699580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266699580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266704877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266704877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266710720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266710720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 17868a62-12db-4006-890c-2d4537b53283"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266743086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266743086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 60f8eb12-34c0-4649-9029-bf39cd2281ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266746019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266746019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 60f8eb12-34c0-4649-9029-bf39cd2281ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266768382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266768381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 60f8eb12-34c0-4649-9029-bf39cd2281ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266768522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266768522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 60f8eb12-34c0-4649-9029-bf39cd2281ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266780557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266780557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266782698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266782698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266784849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266784849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266788099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266788099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266792737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266792737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266805133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266805133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266808006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266808005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266818864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266818863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266819027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266819027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 39a91c6a-16a8-40f7-9b1e-2714bff6fe29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266830832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266830831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266840552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266840552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-10-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266876722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266876722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266905187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266905186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266917817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266917817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266932486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266932486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266938049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266938049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266944120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266944119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266950546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266950545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266957750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266957750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548266982728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548266982728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267005059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267005059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267011910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267011910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" fd7d04b6-0992-4590-9098-9c1f5bbb1a81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267035629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267035629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267043471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267043471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" START_ALICHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267045180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267045180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267046793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267046793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267054614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267054614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267056182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267056182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267059445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267059445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267061023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267061023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267065089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267065089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267066675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267066675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267070223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267070223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" START_ANACHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267072454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267072454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267074016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267074016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267078716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267078716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267080282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267080281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267087449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267087449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267089014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267089014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267093202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267093201"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267094768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267094768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267099008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267099007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267100594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267100594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267110963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267110963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267112572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267112572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267115253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267115253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267117266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267117264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267117468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267117468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 18628c13-57b3-449f-be9c-157b91a5cd4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267145477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267145477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 69cf3237-a3a1-404e-879d-a1b77f97af07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267164639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267164639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 69cf3237-a3a1-404e-879d-a1b77f97af07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267183945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267183945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 69cf3237-a3a1-404e-879d-a1b77f97af07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267203575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267203575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 69cf3237-a3a1-404e-879d-a1b77f97af07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267224573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267224573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 69cf3237-a3a1-404e-879d-a1b77f97af07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267243089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267243088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 69cf3237-a3a1-404e-879d-a1b77f97af07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267243328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267243328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 69cf3237-a3a1-404e-879d-a1b77f97af07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267252939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267252939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_V-A-L"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267256376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267256375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_R-A-H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267265086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267265086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-L-A"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267271745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267271745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_W-E-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267275219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267275219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-W-J"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267278742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267278742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_J-A-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267282277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267282277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_L-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267285456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267285456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-Y-I"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267289273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267289273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-S-E"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267293232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267293232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267299019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267299019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" d6394f32-1072-4ea4-a0cc-c1e1e66af334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267322649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267322649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 711bb929-b184-4d2b-86c9-2ffcd8216663"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267332398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267332395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 711bb929-b184-4d2b-86c9-2ffcd8216663"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267381457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267381457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" 711bb929-b184-4d2b-86c9-2ffcd8216663"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548267416943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548267416943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_200525"," gameId":" e95d9149-ae36-465d-b874-a9342a94535b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}